ILR School Fiscal Office Additional Records /4047
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
ILR School Fiscal Office Additional Records
1971-1976
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
/4047
3 cubic feet
3 linear ft.
Records (documents).
3084983
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
R. Miles, January 13, 2016
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, September 23, 2016
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: /4047 AV: ILR School Fiscal Office Additional Records Audio-Visual Materials
New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations; New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations --Administration.
3084983
- 509-8601 Altro Work Shops Grant (Wasmuth), 1973 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- 509-6802 NYS Ed. Dept., 1971 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- 509-8605 Minority Employment Conf. (Doherty), 1971 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- 509-8607 Title IHEA Consortium on Comm. Crisis (Lindley), 1975 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- 509-8608 Model Programs in Juv. Delinquency (HEW), 1971-1973 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- 509-8612 Rehab. Trng. 615-T-72 (Wasmuth), 1972 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- 509-6813 Jt. Leg. Com. Ind. And Labor Cond. (Donovan) Farm Labor Prj., 1973 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- 509-8616 Dept. of Labor, Manpower and Career Develop. (Gray), 1975 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- 509-8617 Operation Hitchhike (Dennis), 1973 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- 509-8618 NIH - "Diffusion Innov. Medicine" (Huttar), 1974 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- 509-8619 Off to Local Gov't. (Frank), 1973 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- 509-8620 Rehab. Trng. 615-T-73, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- 509-8621 HEW-Comp. Hlth. Plng CP-T00046-01-0, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- 509-8623 (Dennis) Operation Hitchhike, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Mgmt. Dev. Simulation Program (Frank, Wm.), 1974 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- 509-8625 NYC Training Project (Ray Smith), 1974 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- 509-8626 Ford Foundation (Wertheimer), 1972 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- 509-8627 USDL-Impact of Union Mergers etc. (Brooks), 1974 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- 509-8628 Intergovernmental etc. NYC-Hamlin, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- 509-8629 HEW-Lall (Ed. Trng. In NYC), 1974 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- 509-8630 HEW- Wasmuth (Rehabilitation), 1973 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- 509-8631 Ford Foundation (Wertheimer) Women in Unions, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- 509-8632 Proj.(Ford) Worker Exchange (Berry), 1974 (Box 1, Folder 23)
- 509-8634 Local Govt. Career Dev. (Frank), 1975 (Box 1, Folder 24)
- 509-8636 (Wasmuth) Gaps in Delivery of Services to Severely Handicapped, 1974-1975 (Box 1, Folder 25)
- 509-8637 (Wasmuth) Teaching in Rehabilitation Admin., 1974-1975 (Box 1, Folder 26)
- 509-8639 Conf. Labor Mgmt. Practioners (NCOP) (Foltman), 1974-1975 (Box 1, Folder 27)
- 509-8640 Conf. Labor Mgmt. Practitioners (NCOP) (Foltman), 1975 (Box 1, Folder 28)
- 509-8642 (Hamlin) Local Govt. Career Dev., 1975 (Box 1, Folder 29)
- 515-8701 Jt. Railway Labor Hist. (Column), 1974-1975 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- 516-8301 USDL 91-34-69-30 (IRIS), 1974-1975 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- 521-8303 "State of the Art" (USDL) (Freilicher/Cullen), 1972 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- 521-8304 Ford Foundation (Yaffe) Re: Saul Wallen Papers, 1972-1973 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- 521-8305 Proj. 461 "Quality of Works" Ford - Lipsky, 1972-1973 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- 521-8306 (Kochan) Effectiveness Union- Manage. Plant Safety, 1974-1975 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Sub-Grant- University of Wyoming (Kochan) 521-8307, 1974-1975 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- 522-8101 USDL 91-34-69-67 (Tolles/Azevedo) Scientific Personal, 1973-1974 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Omper - USDL (Aronson), 1972-1975 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- 522-8304 (Stoikov) Timing of Retirement, 1972-1975 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- 525-8102 Monnier Fellowship (Timothy) (General Motors), 1973-1975 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- 525-8306 Sears, Roebuck and Co. n(Whyte/Williams), 1971 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- 525-8308 Qual. Of Grad. Educ. NSF GQ-3 (Gordon/Lodahl), 1972 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- 525-8318 Career Award (Whyte) NIMH 21787-08, 1971-1972 (Box 2, Folder 14)
- 525-8319 Soc. Security. Admin. (Gordon), 1971-1972 (Box 2, Folder 15)
- 525-8320 NIMH (Whyte) MH 18171-02, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 16)
- 525-8322 Ford U20-8551 (Whyte), 1972 (Box 2, Folder 17)
- 525-8323 Study of Bureaucracies GS-33509 Meyer, 1972-1974 (Box 2, Folder 18)
- 525-8324 Alcohol Probs - Pols. MH 23237-01 (Trice), 1972-1973 (Box 2, Folder 19)
- 525-8325 Career Awards (Whyte) NIMH, 1972-1973 (Box 2, Folder 20)
- 525-8327 NIH (Whyte) "Employee Participation in, 1973-1974 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Comparative Studies of Soc. Institutions (Whyte) 525-8328, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- 525-8329 Supvr. Reactions to Al. Probs. And Pol. (Trice), 1974 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- 525-8330 Career Awards (Whyte) NiMH 21787-10, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- 525-8331 (Project 486) Miller Fellowship Corning Glass (Miller), 1974 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- 525-8332 David Whetten Support (Aldrich), 1974 (Box 3, Folder 6)
- 525-8333 Hosp. Org. Patient Care (Gordon), 1976 (Box 3, Folder 7)
- 525-8334 (Trice) Supervisor Reactions to Alcohol Probs. And, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 8)
- 526-8304 (VEA-73-8e-738), 1973 (Box 3, Folder 9)
- 526-8304 Apprenticeship Trng. (Foltman), 1973 (Box 3, Folder 10)
- 526-8305 Proj. 459 Conf. on Appren. Trng. (Foltman), 1974 (Box 3, Folder 11)
- 526-8307 Curriculum Dev. Of Related etc. (Foltman), 1974 (Box 3, Folder 12)
- 526-8308 Project No. 488 Women's Studies (Farley) Rochester Telephone, 1973-1974 (Box 3, Folder 13)
- 526-8309 (F. Miller) Operation Hitchhile, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 14)
- 526-8310 (Dyer) Survey Union Leaders and MembersQuality of Working, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 15)
- Instruction in Apprenticeship Research (Foltman), 1974-1975 (Box 3, Folder 16)
- HEW- Soc. And Rehab. And Ser. (Hildebrand), 1972-1973 (Box 3, Folder 17)